A Finding Aid to the Peter Blume Papers, 1870-2001, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artwork, 1932-1984; Series 9; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Box 6-9, OV 10-14
  - Prints and Drawings, Owned by Craton Family, 1936-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Studies, Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Summer, 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hadrian's Villa, circa 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Fracture Ward, circa 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Harps, 1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Obelisk, 1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Boulders of Avila, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Banyan Trees, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Landscape in Bali, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Passage to Etna, circa 1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Castle of Euralus, 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - The Crucifixion and The Shrine, 1951-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Winter, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Crashing Surf, Metamorphosis, Autumn, and Satyr with Cock, 1974-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Oversized material housed in OV 10.
    - Parade, Recollection of the Flood, Tasso's Oak, and The Rock, 1930-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Oversized material housed in OV 11 and OV 14.
    - Doodles, 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
  - Oversized Sketches of Heads scanned with Box 6, F24-28, 1950s-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Artwork by Others scanned with Box 6, F29, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Oversized Studies of Crashing Surf, Metamorphosis, Autumn, and Satyr with Cock scanned with Box 8, Folder 13, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 10, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Studies of Recollection of the Flood and Tasso's Oak scanned with Box 8, Folder 14, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 11, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Studies of The Rock scanned with Box 8, Folder 14, circa 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 14, Folder 1)
    Includes The Rock
  - Oversized Mounted Sketches, Untitled, 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 12, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Mounted Sketches, Untitled, 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 13, Folder 1)
- Craton Family Papers, 1870-2001; Series 10; Archival Resource Key; 0.2 Linear feet Box 6
  This bulk of this series has been scanned; financial records have not been scanned.
  Found are family papers from Grace Blume's brother, James Craton and his wife, Catherine Sears Craton. The bulk of this series relates to the genealogical research performed by Catherine Craton on the Craton and Sears families. These materials include birth, marriage, military, baptismal, and death records, clippings, correspondence, and photographs. Also found is a letter from Grace Blume and an unsigned writing about Peter and Grace Blume by one of their nieces or nephews.
  - Certificates, Birth and Death, 1920-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Certificates, Marriage, 1959-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Burial Records, 1936-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Baptismal Records, 1937-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Wedding Invitation, 1919; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Military Records, Marshall Craton, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Xerox copies of Marshall Craton's Civil War service records including correspondence, payroll and muster rolls. Date determined from the date of the copies.
  - Military Records, James Craton, 1917-1919; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, James and Catherine Craton, 1941-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Regarding Genealogy, 1936-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lists of Family Members, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Instructions for Family Cabin, 2001; 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Financial and Tax Records, 1936-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Clippings, 1911; 1974-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Family Photographs, 1870-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Photocopies, Genealogical Material, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)